<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Klopeiner See Region - Austria</string>

    <!-- Category names -->
    <string name="category_culture">Culture</string>
    <string name="category_family">Family</string>
    <string name="category_active">Active</string>
    <string name="category_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="category_lakes">Lakes</string>

    <!-- LakesFragment strings -->
    <string name="klopeinersee_title">Klopeiner See</string>
    <string name="turnersee_title">Turnersee</string>
    <string name="goesselsdorfersee_titel">Gösselsdorfer See</string>
    <string name="pirkdorfersee_titel">Pirkdorfer See</string>
    <string name="sonneggersee_titel">Sonnegger See</string>
    <string name="linsendorfersee_titel">Linsendorfer See</string>
    <string name="klopeinersee_description">At 28 degrees Celsius, Klopeiner See ranks among the
        warmest bathing lakes in Europe! The excellent drinking water quality attracts those into
        water sports, other water lovers and sunbathers alike. A total of 12 public beach baths
        await families, with everything on hand. The lake promenade of its kind in Austria invites
        you to stroll and enjoy.</string>
    <string name="turnersee_description">Just like its neighbour, Klopeiner See, Turnersee is among
        the warmest bathing lakes in Europe. The idyllic bathing lake with water so clean it is
        drinkable, is a particular must for guests in search of peace and relaxation. You can also
        enjoy a panoramic view of the Karawanken mountains.</string>
    <string name="goesselsdorfersee_description">Gösselsdorfer See is located in the nature reserve
        close to Eberndorf. the public bath is very romantic. If somebody looks for a cosy charming
        lake to enjoy calmness, mountain view and warm bathing, Gösseldorfer See is a must. Tip: a
        wonderful rest for cyclists exploring one of the many marked cycling routes of the region.
    </string>
    <string name="pirkdorfersee_description">The Pirkdorfer See in Southern Carinthia is located at
        the foot of the 2,114 m high Petzen, surrounded by meadows and forests and in the background
        the mountain massif rises like a protective shield.Lake Pirkdorfer presents itself under the
        motto as small but mighty.</string>
    <string name="sonneggersee_description">The Sonnengger lake in the village of Sittersdorf is
        surrounded by a fairytale landscape: clear water, lush meadows, shady forests, fresh
        mountain air. It is particularly suitable for families. Tip: the Acoustic Lakeside Festival
        in July takes place right here on the lake and the Sittersdorfer wine festival in September
        is almost around the corner.</string>
    <string name="linsendorfersee_description">The idyllic resting place in Gallizien in the
        immediate vicinity to the Drau cycling route. Best water quality, a natural lying meadow and
        bathing with free entrance make Lisendorfer an insider tip.</string>
    <string name="klopeinersee_location">geo:0,0?q=Klopeiner See</string>
    <string name="turnersee_location">geo:0,0?q=Turnersee</string>
    <string name="goesselsdorfersee_location">geo:0,0?q=Gösseldorfer See</string>
    <string name="pirkdorfersee_location">geo:0,0?q=Pirkdorfer See</string>
    <string name="sonneggersee_location">geo:0,0?q=Sonnegger See</string>
    <string name="linsendorfersee_location">geo:0,0?q=Linsendorfer See</string>

    <!-- SightsFragment strings -->
    <string name="caves_title">Obir dripstone caves</string>
    <string name="waterfall_title">Wildenstein waterfall</string>
    <string name="troegerner_titel">Trögerner Klamm</string>
    <string name="tscheppa_title">Tscheppaschlucht</string>
    <string name="petzen_title">Mount Petzen cable car</string>
    <string name="cave_description">Nature has been perfecting this work of art for millions of
        years. Visitors to Bad Eisenkappel have three hours to get an inside look at the huge
        stalagmites, stalactites, breathtaking caves and grottos of the Obir dripstone caves.
        They are rank as one of the largest natural monuments in Austria.</string>
    <string name="waterfall_description">The municipality of Gallizien is home to the Wildenstein
        Waterfall, which breaks out of a vertical rock face and drops down 54 metres into the depths
        for a spectacle to admire. Those reaching the Wildenstein waterfall platform can also start
        an equally beautiful but challenging hiking tour on the Hochobir (2,139 metres).</string>
    <string name="troegerner_description">In this wild-romantic canyon landscape, the water has left
        deep incisions in the rock, creating an impressive natural monument. The Trögerner Klamm is
        a hiking and fishing paradise. This 3,5 kilometer long gorge can be wandered on the ground
        or by bicycle.</string>
    <string name="tscheppa_description">The Tscheppaschlucht is a real nature phenomenon. With its
        canyons, cliffs, waterfalls as well as beautiful rare flowers and a marvelous few the
        Tscheppaschlucht is known as a nature jewel. If you are searching for a restorative and
        beautiful nature experience this gorge will not disappoint you.</string>
    <string name="petzen_description">Let the impressions of unspoiled nature enchant you. With the
        Petzen cable car, drive to a height of 1,708 m above sea level and enjoy a view of the Jaun
        valley plus the mountains, hills and lakes of Southern Carinthia. Let the impressions of
        unspoiled nature enchant you.</string>
    <string name="caves_location">geo:0,0?q=Obir Tropfsteinhöhlen, Zauchen</string>
    <string name="waterfall_location">geo:0,0?q=Wildensteiner Wasserfall</string>
    <string name="troegerner_location">geo:0,0?q=Trogener Klamm</string>
    <string name="tscheppa_location">geo:0,0?q=Tscheppaschlucht</string>
    <string name="petzen_location">geo:0,0?q=Petzen-Bergbahnen GmbH</string>

    <!-- ActiveFragment strings -->
    <string name="mtb_title">Mountain biking</string>
    <string name="cycling_title">Road cycling</string>
    <string name="hiking_titel">Hiking</string>
    <string name="golf_title">Golf</string>
    <string name="ski_title">Ski</string>
    <string name="mtb_description">This region is MTB eldorado. Petzen mountain offers the
        highlights most of all. At 11 km long, the Petzen Flow Country Trail is the longest flow
        trail in Europe. The 7 km-long Petzen Thriller is a dream of every enduro rider to test his
        skills on the edge.</string>
    <string name="cycling_description">Road cyclists will find perfect conditions in this area from
        mountain passes with breathtaking views to flat roads along the river Drau. This is where
        the road-bike elite of Austria train. Just drop by at tourist office in Seelach for more
        information and maps.</string>
    <string name="hiking_description">This region is guarded by two giants Hochobir (2139 m) and
        Petzen (2126 m). They are the passport to mountain experiences. By the way do not forget to enjoy
        a pleasant dinner in one of the mountain huts after a grueling hike.</string>
    <string name="golf_description">Discover attractive golfing offers of Golfpark Klopeinersee.
        Sports fans here can look after mind and body, as well as their handicap, who want to
        improve their technique and enjoy views of the Hochobir Mountain and Steiner Alps</string>
    <string name="ski_description">Petzen is just awesome in winter as well. With almost 20 km
        slopes with various levels of difficulty offers it offers unforgettable winter experience.
        Besides Petzen Snow Park welcomes snowboarders and freestyle skiers of all abilities.</string>
    <string name="mtb_location">geo:0,0?q=Petzen-Bergbahnen GmbH</string>
    <string name="cycling_location">geo:0,0?q=Tourismusregion Klopeiner See - Südkärnten</string>
    <string name="hiking_location">geo:0,0?q=Hochobir</string>
    <string name="golf_location">geo:0,0?q=Golfclub/Golfpark Klopeinersee-Südkärnten</string>
    <string name="ski_location">geo:0,0?q=Petzen-Bergbahnen GmbH</string>

    <!-- FamilyFragment strings -->
    <string name="walderlebniswelt_title">Walderlebniswelt Klopeiner See</string>
    <string name="boat_trip_title">Discover Drau by ship</string>
    <string name="bird_park_titel">Turnersee Bird Park</string>
    <string name="sablatnigmoor_title">Sablatnigmoor</string>
    <string name="expi_title">EXPI - Hands on Science Center</string>
    <string name="walderlebniswelt_description">Jumping, climbing, balancing: forest experience
        world at Klopeiner See was created for children and their needs. This is a natural
        playground 20,000 square metres across, boasting over 75 open-air attractions. The
        mini-animal park houses lambs, guinea pigs, donkeys and sheep waiting to meet you. For the
        more inquisitive among you, a nature trail awaits. Children can enjoy this while expanding
        their insights into flora and fauna. The giant sandpit, meanwhile, is a perfect attraction
        for younger guests aged under three years.</string>
    <string name="boat_trip_description">On the Drau, the largest river in Carinthia, the Klopeiner
        See - Südkärnten region offers vacationers a choice of five different pleasure cruises.
        Cruise options include exploring the green canyon and the Devils Islands. Or would you
        rather take a boat and go downtown? If so, then our castle-bridge-city tour will be right
        up your alley. This includes a tour of the Völkermarkt town. Your captain knows this area
        like the back of his hand, including all the old legends and myths. Cabin boys and girls can
        enjoy the pirate control station and childhood captain training at the big steering wheel.
        The older children at heart among you can enjoy a view of the Drava, also through panoramic
        salon windows, or book a romantic evening cruise.</string>
    <string name="bird_park_description">The 300 species presented to visitors are thus mainly the
        product of their offspring. As well as traditional crowd pleasers such as parrots, cockatoo,
        birds of prey or pheasants, the selection includes lesser-known species such as lorikeets or
        Amazons. The tame birds here like nothing better than perching on your arm for a quick feed.
        The latest attraction to reach the bird park is the large terrarium, featuring a frill-necked
        lizard and Barbtail monitor lizards at the entrance. Smaller guests, meanwhile, are likely
        to be entranced by the petting zoo, which features rabbits, guinea pigs, dwarf goats, alpacas
        and ponies, plus an adventure children’s playground and a bouncy castle.</string>
    <string name="sablatnigmoor_description">1,700 animals, 300 plants and 170 bird species are all
        housed in this nature reserve marsh. The site where the present-day Sablatnigmoor has
        established itself was a post-Ice-Age lake some 12,000 years ago. Over time, the area and
        the boggy landscape came into being, bringing with them a rich variety of plant and animal
        life. And something for garden lovers: Featured here are two carnivorous species of sundew
        and waterwash, as well as numerous rare orchids (for example, the marsh sundew). Birds,
        butterflies and frogs are particularly at home in Sablatnigmoor.</string>
    <string name="expi_description">With more than 400 m2 exhibition area and 60 experiemental
        stations, the visitors can experience interesting, surprising and also instructive physical
        phenomena. Watch as a true tornado emerges before your eyes, see with your own eyes how people
        change their size in an "Ames room" or how the "Bernoulli ball" - as held by magic hand -
        floats in the air. Let yourself be surprised by nature!</string>
    <string name="walderlebniswelt_location">geo:0,0?q=Freizeitanlagen Walderlebniswelt Klopeiner See GmbH, Gemeinde Sankt Kanzian am Klopeiner See</string>
    <string name="boat_trip_location">geo:0,0?q=Seidendorf</string>
    <string name="bird_park_location">geo:0,0?q=Vogelpark Turnersee</string>
    <string name="sablatnigmoor_location">geo:0,0?q=Tomerteich</string>
    <string name="expi_location">geo:0,0?q=EXPI Hands on Science Center</string>

    <!-- CultureFragment strings -->
    <string name="sommerspiele_title">Sommerspiele Eberndorf</string>
    <string name="heunburg_title">Theater Heunburg</string>
    <string name="berg_museum_titel">Werner Berg museum</string>
    <string name="liaunig_museum_title">Liaunig museum</string>
    <string name="sommerspiele_description">The South Carinthian summer theater takes place every
        year in July and August in Eberndorf in Carinthia. Founded in 1976, this is one of the largest
        and most famous theater in Carinthia. It is a crucial highlight and jewel in the cultural
        heritage of the Klopeiner See - Südkärnten region.</string>
    <string name="heunburg_description">A higher class theatre with modern plays, this is Heunburg
        theater. It also takes place every year in July and August in Haimburg. In addition to theater,
        a musical night, an opera and operetta evening serve as well for lovers of culture.</string>
    <string name="berg_museum_description">Werner Berg (1904-1981) was honored when the city of
        Bleiburg constructed a monograph museum in 1968. This representative institution, in the
        main square of the city, has since become a mecca for art lovers the world over.</string>
    <string name="liaunig_museum_description">The Liaunig museum showcases one of the best collections
        of Austrian art from 1945 onwards, complemented by some dazzling artwork from international
        artists. Another highlight awaiting all art lovers is the pair of art and culture bike paths.
    </string>
    <string name="sommerspiele_location">geo:0,0?q=Sommerspiele Eberndorf</string>
    <string name="heunburg_location">geo:0,0?q=Heunburg Theater</string>
    <string name="berg_museum_location">geo:0,0?q=Werner Berg Museum</string>
    <string name="liaunig_museum_location">geo:0,0?q=Museum Liaunig</string>
</resources>
